aioapps.com 2015-11-20

# Privacy Policy | All-In-One Apps

**Your privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, [AIOapps.com](http://aioapps.com/ "http://AIOapps.com") makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
[AIOapps.com](http://aioapps.com/ "http://AIOapps.com") does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**The DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables them to serve ads to users based on their visit to this website and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – [www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html")

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [AIOapps.com](http://aioapps.com/ "http://AIOapps.com") send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

[AIOapps.com](http://aioapps.com/ "http://AIOapps.com") has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. [AIOapps.com](http://aioapps.com/ "http://AIOapps.com")‘s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

**Links to third party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of [AIOapps.com](http://aioapps.com/ "http://AIOapps.com") then you may contact us at [aioapps.contact@gmail.com](mailto:aioapps.contact@gmail.com "mailto:aioapps.contact@gmail.com")
